很高兴为大家介绍这位激励了我很多年的女人
I'm honored to introduce the woman who's been an inspiration of mine for years.
连任州长Melcher
她向本州女性朋友们证明
She's shown the women of this state
只要矢志不渝 女人没什么做不到的
that if we put our minds to it, anything is possible.
女州长? 真恶心
A female Governor? Ewe, yuck!
难道只有我一个人恨女人吗?
Am I the only one who hates women?
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
有请现任以及下任州长 Nina Melcher
the current and future Governor, Nina Melcher!
早上好 脆莓
Good morning, Brickleberry.
很荣幸能给大家演讲...
It's such an honor to speak to...
我是来看州长的 不是他家土里土气的老妈子
I'm here to see the Governor, not his frumpy housekeeper!
Woody 你特么怎么回事?
Woody! What the hell is your problem?
他早上喝酒来着 看他酒疯耍到什么程度
He drank his breakfast. Let's see where this goes.
我来告诉你我怎么回事
I'll tell you what my problem is!
我可不想让一个自大的女州长对我指手画脚
I don't want some uppity she-Governor telling me what to do!
在此我提出一个文明合理的建议
I'm here to lodge an intelligent protest!
给我们看你咪咪 给我们看你咪咪
Show your tits! Show your tits! Show your tits!
我跟她说话呢 你个白痴
I was talking to her, you idiot!
Steve 你的咪咪也不错
Hey, Steve, you got nice tits.
先生 你还有别的要跟我说吗?
Sir, is there something you would like to say to me?
有啊 操蛋州长 这就说
Yes, Governor "Felcher," there is!
在光荣的700年里 这个国家一直由男性主导
For 700 proud years, this country was run by men!
充满着勇气 态度 耷拉着大屌的男人们
All courage, attitude, and big, swinging sausage.
但当"女人们"掌权之后
But then "women" got put in charge.
会怎么样呢? 把卫生棉定做国鸟?
What's next? Making the tampon the official state bird?
或者卫生巾 人家有护"翼"
Or Maxi Pads. They have wings.
我奉劝您保持安静 对我尊重一点
I suggest that you be quiet and show a little respect,
不然你会后悔的
or you'll regret it.
都快逃命啊 大家伙儿 她要爆发了
Run for cover, everybody! She's having a hot flash!
闭上你那张性别歧视臭嘴
Shut your sexist mouth!
不然她能把我怎样?
Oh, what's she gonna do?
搞你妹啊?
What the hell?
"性别歧视傻X Woody Johnson 纪念高速路"?
"The Woody Johnson is a sexist asshole memorial highway"?
不
No!
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
林警站
翻译 白云苍狗
她把该死的高速路修在我的公园里?
She built a goddamn highway through my park!
翻译 偏执绝非过错
也许下次你就得在和州长起冲突之前好好考虑一下了
Well, maybe next time, you'll think twice about picking a fight with the Governor.
翻译 井脑湿
人家不是好惹的
She's a pit bull.
翻译 Chubby
算你走运 我找不出一个关于母狗的贬义词
Well, you're just lucky that I can't think of a derogatory term for "female dog".
后期 旗木&盖罗
我想到个... Connie
I've got one... Connie.
你要是真想让那条高速路消失 就去跟州长道歉
If you want that highway gone, you should apologize to the Governor.
我绝不向女人道歉
I will never apologize to a woman!
如果这点困扰你了 Ethel 我向你道歉
And if that bothers you, Ethel, well, I apologize.
你这不就道歉了嘛
But you just apologized.
甭用你那套白痴的理论跟我逼逼
Don't trap me with your goopy vagina logic!
天呐 Woody 你妈都对你做了什么?
Jesus, Woody, what did your mother do to you?
我妈是个圣人
My mother was a Saint.
我太为你骄傲了 儿子 八岁生日快乐
I'm so proud of you, son. Happy eighth birthday.
赶紧 把这妓女上了 你就不会变成基佬咯
Now, screw this hooker so you don't turn into a queer.
Woody就是这么遇见他第一任老婆的
And that's how Woody met his first wife.
早上好呀 林警们
Good morning, rangers.
"滚回非洲去 黑鬼"
"Go back to Africa, negro".
- Woody - 干嘛 读他衣服上的字而已
- Woody! - What? I was just reading his shirt.
滚回非洲去 黑鬼
一群乡巴佬给的
Some rednecks gave it to me.
他们在外边招兵组建武装组织呢
They're outside, recruiting for their militia.
但你为啥要穿这玩意?
But why are you wearing it?
我才不关心上面写啥 反正是免费的
I don't give a shit what it say. It's a free T-shirt.
我超喜欢 有骂波多黎各人的吗?
I like it. Does it come in Puerto Rican?
该死 现在又得对付一群武装组织了?
Oh, crap. Now we got a militia to deal with?
算哥时运不济 Steve 去搞掉他们
This is not my week. Steve, go take care of it!
Steve特么跑哪去了?
Where the hell is Steve?
救命?
Help?
Steve完犊子了 Connie 去解决他们
Ah, screw Steve. Connie, go take care of it!
会议地点
武装团伙令晚集会
武装团伙就在这开会吗?
Uh, is this the militia meeting?
- 我来这儿是要... - 是啊 你想加入吗?
- I was sent here to... - Yeah! You wanna join?
- BoDean 你有病啊? - 咋? 咱们需要人手 Bobby
- BoDean, what the hell? - What? We need members, Bobby.
咱反基佬的 还记得吗?
We're anti-gay, remember?
反同性恋
她就是基佬
She's a gay.
是啊 Bobby 俺记得
Yeah, Bobby, I remember,
但她看起来挺壮 也没别人会加入了
but she looks strong and nobody else will join.
你疯哥不愿意加入 你残姐不愿意加入
Not even your crazy brother or your crippled sister
你那曾想咬掉我二弟的婊子姨妈都不愿加入
or your dirty whore Aunt who tried to bite my peter off.
有道理 好吧 俺要宣布一件事
Good point. Okay, I got an announcement to make.
你可以加入 俺们现在挺基佬了
You can join. We are now pro-gay.
太好了 太好了 太好了
Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
以前还从没人邀请我加入社团呢
Nobody ever asked me to join a club before.
这是你的免费T恤衫
And here's your free T-shirt.
好耶 免费T恤衫
Yay! Free T-shirt!
滚回非洲去 黑鬼 基佬
汤怎么样?
How's the soup?
- 啥? - 汤
- What? - Soup!
- 大便? - 不是 汤
- Poop? - No! Soup!
我知道
I know!
我说你做的汤喝起来像大便
I'm saying your soup tastes like shit.
尼玛
Damn it!
你确定不要去道歉?
You sure you don't want to apologize?
绝不 塞翁失马焉知非福
Never! We are gonna make the best of this!
这特么又是哪来的?
Where the [Bleep] did that come from?
- 你谁啊? - 天呐 你能开门真是太好了
- And who the hell are you? - Man, I'm glad you're open.
开好几英里才找到休息站NThis is the first rest stop for miles.
我得借光赶紧撒泡尿去
I gotta squeak a leak out of my crotch beak.
什么情况?
What the hell?
你是这儿管事的吗? 我好像把马桶弄坏了
Hey, are you the manager? I think I broke your shitter.
不过不用担心 还有人在用呢
But don't worry. People are still using it.
- 搞毛... - 你说"塞翁失马焉知非福"嘛
- What the... - You said, "make the best of it".
请付美金 香烟 玉米卷 汽水 热狗
够了 我没耐心将就下去了
That's it! I can't take it anymore!
Aabheer 你得提前值班了
Aabheer, your shift's starting early.
中奖噜
Jackpot.
你能来道歉挺不容易 让人觉得你温情尚存
I think it's great that you're apologizing. It shows your sensitive side.
你买的是什么花? 三色堇?
Hey, what kind of flowers are those? Pansies?
不 这是一束"尼玛拆了高速路"花
No, they're a bouquet of shut-the-[Bleep]-upsies.
只要能把高速路弄出公园 怎么着都行
I'll do anything to get that highway out of my park.
天 这宅子真棒
Wow! Nice mansion!
为啥我们没有这样一套宅子?
Why don't we live in a place like this?
对哦 因为人家那位女州长比你还爷们呢
Oh, right! Because that lady Governor is more of a man than you are.
你好 州长
Hello, Governor.
是你啊
Oh, it's you.
有话快说 Johnson 我快误了一场重要讲话了
Make it fast, Johnson. I'm late for a very important speech.
只占用你几秒钟时间
This will only take a second.
我只想说我抱-抱-抱-抱-抱...
I just wanted to say I'm s-s-s-s-s-s...
真娘
Such a pussy.
我抱...
I'm sor...
很抱歉 在我说出真相时
I'm sorry that you felt threatened
你被我的男子气概震得眼泪汪汪
by my manhood and got all weepy when I told the truth!
- 好了 - 这就是你的道歉?
- There. - That's your apology?
还有这个
Plus these.
大部分糖都被他在路上给吃光了
He ate most of the candy on the way here.
看你这大屁股 我算帮了你大忙呢
And judging by your ass, I did you a favor.
开玩笑的 你屁股也没... 好吧
Kidding. Your ass isn't that, well...
还真大 但是我还是算助人为乐对吧
It's pretty big, but, hey, I'd still do you with the lights off.
能不计前嫌了?
So, friends again?
我可以向你保证一件事 Johnson先生
I can promise you one thing, Mr. Johnson.
只要我在州长位置上做一日 高速公路就不会移动一寸
As long as I'm Governor of this state, that highway won't move an inch!
什么? 你竟敢这样对我 你个死贱...
What? You can't do this to me, you dirty c...
现在 我得走了
Now, if you'll excuse me.
看来货车站还是会在 好吧
So, the truck stop stays. All right.
寻欢洞: 在木板或墙壁中间戳洞 双方开始鱼水之欢
人家还得滚回家补寻欢洞去...
I gotta get home and patch up some glory holes.
慌什么 我还没完呢
Not so fast! I ain't done yet.
闪边去 女士 我要发表我的演讲
Step aside, lady! I got my own announcement to make.
我 Woodrow Wayland Johnson 将竞选州长
I, Woodrow Wayland Johnson, am running for Governor!
有问题吗? 你 穿黑衣的女士
Any questions? Yes, the lady dressed in black.
你跑我儿子葬礼上宣布个球?
Why are you announcing this at my son's funeral?
一路走好
选Woody当州长
福克斯新闻刚说同性恋恐怖分子
Fox news just said that gay terrorists
正在试图用堕胎取代我们的枪支
are trying to replace our guns with abortions.
这就是为什么Woody要竞选州长
That's why Woody needs to be Governor.
只要把筹款单给Malloy就行了
Just make that donation check out to Malloy.
大伙们 Steve呼叫
Hey, guys! It's Steve!
我被困在高速公路中间很多天了
I've been trapped for days in the middle of the highway!
请派...
Please send...
好了 Woody选民队 咱们筹到多少款了?
All right, team Woody! How much money have we raised?
三万美元
$30,000.
哎呦 抱歉 负债三万美元
Oops, sorry. Negative $30,000.
什么?
What?
印传单要钱 广播广告要钱
There's the printing, the radio spots,
还有那头你为就职典礼准备的海豚
uh, and that dolphin for your inauguration.
恭喜你 Woody州长
我那是一时冲动买的 但我不后悔
It was an impulse buy, but I don't regret it.
Melcher选举必胜
敢在我竞选办公室里穿这衣服 你胆子可真不小
You've got a lot of nerve, wearing that in my campaign office.
这儿不是你竞选办公室 Woody
It's not your campaign office, Woody.
这儿是林警站
It's the ranger station.
- 地狱烈焰里受死吧 犹太人 - 什么?
- Burn in hell, Jew. - What?
又是免费民兵衫 对吧Denzel?
Oh, more free militia T-shirts, Denzel?
GAP: 美国老牌服装零售商
不 这件在GAP买的
No, I got this at the GAP.
听着 Woody 你没机会赢的
Look, Woody, you don't stand a chance.
Melcher州长提高了就业率
Governor Melcher cut unemployment,
还清了债务 还赢过一次国会荣誉勋章
she balanced the budget, and won a Congressional Medal of Honor.
而你是歧视妇女的种族偏见战犯
You're a racist, misogynistic war criminal!
如果你用这种口吻来说 听起来还真是那回事
Well, when you say it with that negative tone, it sounds bad, yeah.
Woody 你必须得赢
Woody, here's the deal.
只有赢得这场选举 我才有机会入住州长官邸
I need you to win so I can live in the Governor's mansion.
我可是跟一个娘们拉选票呢 怎么可能会输呢
I'm running against a woman. Of course I'm going to win.
你只有1%的支持率
You're trailing in the polls by 99%!
我们得下点猛药才行
We need to do something drastic.
没错 我们得再买条海豚
You're right! We should buy another dolphin!
不 让我们背后黑了这娘们
No! Let's blackmail this woman.
好点子
That's smart.
让她背点黑锅 让她无地自容
Get some dirt on her, hold it over her head.
不 我是说"黑人" 就是你
No. I said, "black male," I.E., you.
你得跟她嘿咻再录下来
You're gonna make a sex tape with her.
对 然后我们边看边打飞机
Yeah, then we can whack off to it.
不 我们会把视频寄给媒体
No, we will send it to the press.
你有你办法 我有我主意
You do it your way, I'll do it mine.
爱爱和电视我倒都喜欢 但她有多老了?
I do love sex and electronics. But how old is she?
- 别担心 她年纪可不小 - 听到了没 鸡鸡?
- Don't worry. She's old. - Hey, did you hear that, Dick?
硬了没? 看起来你确实硬了
You excited? Looks like you are!
不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
见鬼了
Damn it!
BoDean 俺没要你把它吞下去 把它含在嘴里就行了
BoDean, I'm not asking you to suck it. Just hold it in your mouth.
- 欢迎回来 会员 - 好消息 大伙们
- Welcome, member! - Guys, I got great news.
- 我带了个新会员来 他是我的生活教练
I brought a new recruit! He's my life Coach.
大伙好
Hola.
不不 不要墨西哥佬
No, no, no! No Mexicans!
俺们和墨西哥佬水火不容
We are definitely anti-Mexican!
但他有油煎面卷饼啊
But he brought Chimichangas!
- 这些玩意真好吃 Bobby - 好 得了 你留下吧
- These are real good, Bobby. - Okay, fine! You can join.
谢谢 朋友们
Gracias, amigo.
这话翻成墨西哥语是"玉米卷圣诞"
That's "burrito Christmas" in Mexican.
Epstein鸡尾酒吧
你好啊 性感州长
Hey, hey, sexy Governor.
我不是州长 那边那位才是州长
I'm not the Governor. That's the Governor.
什-什么?
Www-w-what?
我得告诉你个坏消息 鸡鸡
I've got some bad news for you, Dick.
需搭便车过街
要带你走多远 哥们?
How far are you going, friend?
过街就行
Across the street.
很好 这就带你过去
Cool. I'll take you there.
对了 你不介意在我父母的家门口等我一下吧?
Say, do you mind if we make a quick stop by my parents' house?
最近的天气有点反常 不是吗?
Crazy weather we've had lately, huh?
- 你刚说要我带你上哪? - 过街就行
- Where'd you say you were going? - Uh, across the street.
很好 正好经过我妹妹家门口
Cool! That's on the way to my sister's house.
与黑人男子性爱的录影带流出之后
Governor Melcher has dropped out of the race
Melcher州长在大选中不幸落马
after the release of a sex tape with a black male.
黑人男子性丑闻
完蛋
日啊 这对胸真是又丰满又坚挺
Damn, your breasts are so firm and perky.
谢谢
Thank you.
那不是称赞好吧
That wasn't no compliment!
- Denzel 你怎么可以这样? - 哥也不容易啊
- Denzel, how could you? - Whew! It wasn't easy.
当时只好紧闭双眼
I had to close my eyes
想像着伊丽莎白女王和布什他老婆玩劈胯
and think about Queen Elizabeth scissoring Barbara Bush.
靠啊 Woody 你实在是太没下限了
Damn it, Woody! This is low, even for you.
想知道下限何在吗 Ethel? 等老子当了州长
You want to see low, Ethel? Wait till I'm Governor.
到时你不用穿蒙面长袍上街就该谢天谢地了
You'll be lucky to go outside without a goddamn burqa!
我绝对不会让你毫无对手地当选的
There's no way I'm letting you run unopposed.
那会有谁敢挑战我?
Well, who's going to challenge me?
我就此宣布参加州长竞选
I would like to announce my candidacy for Governor!
你们这些人能不能放我家一马?
Why won't you people leave our family alone?
♪ 我是州长 欢迎围观 ♪
♪ I'm the Governor, look at me! ♪
♪ 我是州长 万人景仰 ♪
♪ Everybody loves me, I'm the Governor! ♪
♪ 我是州长 我是州长 ♪
♪ I'm the Governor, I'm the Governor! ♪
♪ 我就是州长 ♪
♪ I'm the Governor! ♪
求你闭嘴好么?
Can you please shut up?
我在为州长官邸网购90英寸大电视呢
I'm trying to pick out a 90-inch TV for the Governor's mansion.
慢着 Malloy
Whoa, Malloy.
你真的以为你会跟我一起住大官邸啊?
Do you really think you're going to live in the Governor's mansion with me?
- 天真了吧? - 你啥意思?
- Do you? - What do you mean?
对不起啦 小盆友 州长不会跟熊孩子住一块的
I'm sorry, little buddy, but governors don't live with bears.
你个阴险的死叛徒 是我成就了你
You backstabbing turncoat. I made you.
Malloy 咱俩的关系可得保持低调 就这么个事儿
Malloy, we'll just have to keep our relationship on the down low, that's all.
人们已经开始觉得诡异了
Everybody already thinks it's weird.
诡异? 林肯还跟袋鼠玩过口活
Weird? Lincoln sucked off a kangaroo.
好好去学下历史
Read a history book.
综上所述 如果你向往着 各种族和平共处
And so, if you want a state where all races live in peace
红肉含有高饱和脂肪 不及其他肉健康
没有战争 没有富人 没有红肉
and harmony without war, rich people, or red meat,
坠胎算是唯一的暴力犯罪
and the only violent acts committed are against unborn babies,
那么你们应该选我
you should vote for me.
挺棒的 Ethel
That's great, Ethel.
Connie 别捧我 你是来扮演Woody的
Connie, come on. You're supposed to pretend to be Woody.
对不起 我忘了
Sorry, that's right.
老子是Woody
Argh! I'm Woody!
Connie 你个大傻X 快去摆平那些民兵
Connie, you stupid [Bleep]! Go get rid of that militia!
不行 Woody 他们是我朋友
No, Woody. They're my friends.
你他娘的闭嘴 Connie 你个万人嫌
Shut the hell up, Connie! Everybody hates you!
整天又跑又哭的 也不见她瘦点
All that running and crying, you'd think she'd be thinner.
Ethel 你好哇
Ethel! How are you?
- 有屁快放 - 我在想啊
- What do you want? - Just thinking.
咱俩完全可以做闺蜜呢
I could see us actually becoming pretty good friends.
那啥 等你当上州长 咱俩一起住官邸的时候
You know, when you're Governor and we're both living at the Governor's mansion.
你想跟我一起搬进州长官邸住着?
You want to move into the Governor's mansion with me?
幻想下 半夜三更咱们穿着睡衣
Think of all the late nights we'd spend in our PJs,
《恋恋笔记本》男主角
舔着哈根达斯啊 看着Ryan Gosling撸一管啊
binging on Haagen-dazs, rubbing our beavs to Ryan Gosling.
你明白我永远不可能跟你住一起的吧 永远不会
You do realize that there's absolutely no way I'd ever live with you, ever.
自打我来到这儿 你一直都没让我过个好日子
You've been trying to ruin my life ever since I got here.
闺蜜你真傻 我都是闹着玩呢亲
Girl, you so crazy. It was all in fun.
我的答案是 绝逼不行
The answer is hell no.
老子要让你暴尸街头血流满地
The streets will run red with your blood.
砖家们说冥王星不再算作行星的时候
So, when they said Pluto was no longer a planet,
真是让我气爆了
well, that really ticked me off!
我疯了是吧?
Am I crazy?
我倒没看出来
Not from where I'm sitting.
知道还有谁喜欢冥王星吗? 我妹妹
You know who else likes Pluto? My sister.
你猜怎么着 大哥?
Guess what, big brother.
咋啦 小妹?
What, little sister?
冥王星不算行星了哟
Pluto's not even a planet anymore.
闭上你的烂嘴 臭三八
Shut your lying mouth, you bitch!
不好意思 兄妹拌嘴嘛
Sorry. Sibling rivalry.
她... 看起来是个好人
She... she seems nice.
我日啊
God damn it!
"明"兵野餐会
大家伙儿 这集会真棒 对吧?
You guys. What a great militia meeting, right?
看看咱们的新成员
Look at all these new members.
随便啦 少逼逼 快把民兵奶酪通心粉递过来
Yeah, yeah. Shut your face and pass the militia mac and cheese.
这货是特么谁叫来的?
Who the hell invited this guy?
我们绝对反... 反...
We are definitely anti... anti...
你到底是个啥玩艺儿?
What the hell are you, anyway?
我也不知道呀
I have no idea!
这就挺不错啦 Bobby
This is awesome, Bobby.
咱的队员人数达到了史上最高
Our membership is at an all-time high.
跨文化兵团是不是感觉高端多了?
And isn't having a multicultural militia so much nicer?
我想是吧 兵团不是要发表宣言什么的吗?
Yeah, I guess so, but don't militias need to make some sort of statement?
对 的确要这样
Yes, you do.
首先 民兵是不野餐的
First of all, militias don't have picnics.
那民兵都搞啥啊?
Well, what do militias do?
暴动啊 你们怎么可能不知道呢?
Violent acts. How do you not know this?
你们看起来更像少数民族书友会
You guys look more like the Ellis Island Book Club.
Malloy 你这是干嘛?
Malloy, what are you doing?
闭嘴 Etheridge战士
Quiet, militia Etheridge.
让这只说话熊把话说完
Let the talking bear finish talking.
如果你们想玩真格的
If you want to be a real militia,
必须抛头露面做点大事
you need to stand up and do something big,
具有毁灭性的 可以载入史册的那种大事
something destructive, something that puts you in the history books.
比如发明双头震动棒的那货
Like that guy who invented the double-donged dildo!
能让他闭嘴吗?
Can he not talk?
让全世界听到我们声音的时候到了
It's time to make a statement the world will hear!
- 没错 算俺们一个 - 好啊
- Hell yeah! Count us in! - Yes!
终于特么有点民兵的样子了
It's time we started acting like a real [Bleep] militia!
脆莓大讲堂 州长候选人辩论
州长候选人辩论赛
我们的孩子考试成绩正在以惊人速度下降
Our children's test scores have been dropping at an alarming rate.
有何计划呢 Johnson先生?
What is your plan, Mr. Johnson?
主持人
听好了 呆逼 这块地盘上只有老子才能提问
Listen, chuckles. I'll be asking the questions around here.
你不行 人家是主持人
No, you won't. He's the moderator.
不是喽 老子现在是主持喽
Not anymore. I'm the moderator now.
♪ 我是主持人 欢迎围观 ♪
♪ I'm the moderator, look at me! ♪
♪ 我是主持人 万人景仰 ♪
♪ Everybody loves me, I'm the moderator! ♪
♪ 我是主持人 我是主持人 ♪
♪I'm the moderator, I'm the moderator! ♪
♪ 我就是主持人 ♪
♪I'm the moderator! ♪
下面请观众直接发问吧
Let's just take some questions from the audience.
朕许了
I'll allow it.
大家好啊
Hello, everybody.
俺是"少数民族书友会兵团"的大首领
I'm the leader of the Ellis Island Book Club militia.
俺们决定要刺杀新任州长
And we have decided to assassinate the new Governor,
所以甭管你们谁赢了 都得死
so whichever one of y'all wins, you're dead!
祝各位竞选愉快
Y'all have a nice day.
给我听着 我对威胁不予回应
Listen here. I don't respond to threats.
一直都有人告诉我 因为我是个女人 所以应该放弃
All my life, I've been told that because I'm a woman, I should give up.
你听着 我会...
Well guess what! I'm...
我将立即退出州长竞选
Dropping out of the race for Governor immediately.
不对不对不对 我才会退出竞选
No, no, no, no. I'm dropping out of the race.
才不 是我先退出的
No, you're not! I dropped out first.
我比你更有资格退出竞选
I'm much more qualified to drop out of this race than you!
轮不到你来说 我不能退出竞选
You can't tell me that I can't drop out of this race.
有谁能帮忙叫辆救护车吗?
Would someone please call me an ambulance?
老天 这家伙问题真特么多
Jesus! This guy asks a lot of [Bleep] questions!
- Malloy? - 干嘛 Connie?
- Uh, Malloy? - Yes, Connie?
你能加入我们的组织 我真的很高兴 但是...
I'm really happy you joined our militia and everything, but, uh,
我觉着你那个暗杀州长的主意有些不妥
I'm not so sure about your idea to violently assassinate the Governor.
放心 Connie 不会有人受伤的
Relax, Connie. No one's gonna get hurt.
- 真的吗? - 真的
- Really? - Really.
我就是想吓吓他们 好让他们退出竞选
I just want to scare them into dropping out of the race.
要是我不能住进州长官邸 谁也甭想
If I can't live in the Governor's mansion, neither can they.
相信我 今天没人会死的
Trust me. No one's gonna die today.
今天某些人是死定了
Someone's definitely going to die today,
只要Woody Johnson和Ethel Anderson依然是候选人
as Woody Johnson and Ethel Anderson's names will remain on the ballot
谁将死?
不管他们退出与否
whether they drop out or not.
也就是说他们中有一人会被选为州长
Which means one of them will be elected Governor
并转眼被杀
and swiftly assassinated.
我是瞎话篓子
Ain't I a stinker?
我是Ethel Anderson
Hi, I'm Ethel Anderson,
本人绝不应该被选为州长
and there's no way that I should be elected Governor.
你问为什么?
Why, you say?
因为我是个死不悔改的狂暴酒鬼
Because I'm a raging, unrepentant alcoholic,
而且我相信希特勒绝没屠杀犹太人 但我希望他有
and I believe the holocaust never happened, but I wish it did.
请为Woody Johnson投票
Vote Woody Johnson for Governor.
恶搞罗斯福炉边谈话
大家好 我是Woody Johnson 没必要兜圈子了
Hi, I'm Woody Johnson, and there's no use beating around the bush.
我猥亵儿童 而且乐此不疲
I molest kids, and I love it.
儿童猥亵狂
禁止通行
并且我保证会把本州变成恐怖分子的天堂
And I promise to make this state a safe haven for terrorists.
我能说"去他妈的军队"吗?
Hey, can I just say, "[Bleep] Our troops"?
看我把自由女神像插哪儿了?
Look where I can stick the Statue of Liberty!
女性庇护所
家庭暴力不是个问题
Domestic violence isn't a problem...
而是个方案
It's a solution.
♪ 美国歌谣《凯卜镇赛马Camptown Races》
♪ 凯卜镇唱起歌呀 ♪
♪ Camptown lady's sing this song... ♪
♪ 嘟哒 嘟哒 ♪
♪ Doo-dah. Doo-dah. ♪
选Woody
竞选结果已出
And the election results are in.
州长竞选
如果我当选 我就脱离群众
If I win, I am dropping off the grid.
再改个不起眼的名字 比如...
I'll change my name to something inconspicuous like...
- 剑火Rick - 想得真美
- Rick Swordfire. - Yeah, good thinking.
竞选州长的胜者是...
The winner, and new state Governor is...
- Woody Johnson - 什么?
- Woody Johnson. - What?
呼你熊脸 大死人
In your face, dead man!
以2:0选票之差险胜竞选
By the remarkably low count of two votes to none.
等下 你给自己投票了?
Wait. You voted for yourself?
难不成还要我给天杀的女人投票?!
Well I wasn't gonna vote for a goddamn woman.
你好啊 州长先生
Hello, Mr. Governor.
你找错人了 我叫剑火Rick
You've got the wrong guy, my name is Rick Swordfire.
我认识剑火Rick 而你 先生 不是剑火Rick
I knew Rick Swordfire, and you, Sir, are no Rick Swordfire!
恶搞拉丁语名言Et tu, Brute? 后世普遍认为
是罗马晚期独裁官儒略·恺撒临死前最后一句话
还有你 Malloy?
Et tu, Malloy?
嘿 谁让你不带我住州长官邸
Hey, you wouldn't let me live in the Governor's mansion.
好吧 你可以住在州长官邸
Okay! You can live in the Governor's mansion!
你可以住主卧 我就去睡马桶 我不管
You can have the Master Bedroom! I'll sleep in the shitter! I don't care!
- 快叫他们停下 - 真的?
- Just talk them down! - Really?
好的伙计们 有好消息
Okay, guys, great news.
放下武器 刺杀行动失败
Put down your guns. The assassination is a no go.
屁扯
Oh, hell no!
你不能把人家弄得欲火焚身了 再把人家晾在那里
You can't get a militia all hot and bothered and leave 'em hanging like that.
是时候爆烂他的菊花了
It's time to bust a nut in his ass!
我是说打爆他的头
Uh, I mean cap.
我们可以包揽
We can do both!
住手
Stop!
- Ethel 怎么... - 闭嘴 Woody
- Ethel? What are... - Shut up, Woody.
让女人给这帮白痴讲讲道理
Let a woman talk some sense into these idiots.
走开 大波女 我们有信息要传达
Out of the way, two tits! We have a message to send!
杀了这么一个悲剧的人渣...
What kind of message could you possibly want to send
又能帮你们传达什么信息?
by killing this pathetic piece of shit?
俺们要杀了他 因为他所代表的政府
We're gonna kill him because he represents a government
被犹太复国主义者控制了
controlled by the zionist Jew threat!
Bobby 咱们不反犹太人了现在
Bobby, we're okay with Jew people now.
是Chaim从他的服装厂给咱们搞来的制服
Chaim got us these uniforms from his garment factory.
好吧 其实俺是想说 俺们要杀他
Fine, what I meant to say was, we gonna kill him
是因为他想让肮脏的移民冲垮俺们的海岸
because he wants to flood our shores with dirty immigrants.
移民也是好人 你忘啦?
Immigrants are good, remember?
陈教授给咱们洗衣服
Professor Chin did all our laundry,
Patel博士开出租载咱们来的
and Dr. Patel drove us here in his cab.
干 还有啥东西能让俺们反的嘛?!
Aw, shit, are we anti-anything anymore?
我知道该反啥了
I know what we are!
我们是反白人的垃圾男
We're anti-white garbage trash man!
各位 停下 我有个想法
Guys! Stop! I got an idea.
不如把我们的组织设定为反暴力?
How about if we make our militia all about being anti-violence?
去你的
Screw it.
- 我们赶紧走吧 你觉得呢 - 不能同意更多
- You think we can just leave? - I don't see why not.
Ethel 是你救了我
Ethel, you saved my life.
你向我证明了 女人可以从事伟大的事业
You've proved to me that women are capable of great things.
我错了 对不起
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
你第一次向女人道歉
Your first female apology.
我把厌女混蛋做绝了 但你还是救了我 为什么?
I did act like a misogynist asshole, yet you still saved me. Why?
因为也许我们性别不同
Because even though we may be different genders,
但骨子里都是流淌着红色血液的...
deep down inside, we're both red-blooded...
白人 万岁
White people. High five!
- 不是 其实我是想说... - 嘘 就这么着吧
- No, actually, I was going to say... - Shh-shh. We'll leave it at that.
作为州长 我很高兴得宣布我的第一个任务
I am pleased to announce that my first act as your Governor
恭喜Johnson州长
那就是拆除横跨脆莓公园的高架桥
is to remove the highway running through Brickleberry Park.
施工队已经准备就绪
The wrecking crew is already on its way.
好了 Phil 你的家人真是贴心
Ah, well, Phil, your family is great company,
但我们已经连续玩了六天了
but we've been playing for six straight days.
我们才刚开始呢
We're just getting started.
哎呀 你忘了说"哦不"
Uh-oh. You forgot to say, "Uno"!
直升机 谢天谢地我得救了
A helicopter! Thank God! I'm saved!
哦不
Uno!
拆除之后 我将辞去州长一职
And with that done, I'm stepping down as Governor.
为了感谢我的朋友Ethel
As a thank you to my friend Ethel,
我的最后一个任务是原谅Melcher州长
my last act is to pardon Governor Melcher
和一位黑人同志录制性爱录像带
for her having sex on tape with a black guy
并把州长工作交还给她
and hand the job back to her.
- 谢谢你 Woody - 回来真好
- Thank you, Woody! - It's good to be back.
她又是州长了?
She Governor again?
你让我无缘无故的小牛吃嫩草?
You made me rob the cradle for nothing?
等一下 你是性爱录像的主谋?
Wait a minute. You were behind that sex tape?
覆水难收了 不是吗?
Water under the bridge, right?
"专为爆菊狂准备的Woody Johnson囚牢"?
"The Woody Johnson prison for criminally insane man-rapists"?
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons